lifewithoutlimbs.org 2019-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Life Without Limbs

LIFE WITHOUT LIMBS’ PRIVACY POLICY

Revised 5.25.2018

At Life Without Limbs, we strive to develop innovative services to better serve our users. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use Life Without Limbs services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it, and how to withdraw consent.

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. “Personally identifying information” is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address.

**Data collection**  
Some services do not require any personally identifying information. Some of our services require you to register for an account.  In order to create an account users are asked for personally identifying information (typically your name, email address and a password for your account) and we will use that information to provide the service. For certain services and product purchases we may request credit card or other payment information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers.

When we require personally identifying information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.

**Withdraw Consent**

If you don’t want us to process your data anymore, please contact us at 818-706-3300, or send an email to info@lifewithoutlimbs.org or send us mail to PO Box 2430, Agoura Hills, CA  91376.

**Cookies**  
Upon your first visit to Life Without Limbs, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. Life Without Limbs does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people utilize our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Life Without Limbs features or services may not function properly without cookies.

**Information sharing**  
WE DO NOT RENT OR SELL YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION TO OTHER COMPANIES OR INDIVIDUALS, UNLESS WE HAVE YOUR CONSENT. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Life Without Limbs, its users or the public.
  * If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.
  * We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which Life Without Limbs or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of Life Without Limbs, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Information security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.

We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

**Updating your information**  
We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. For more information, please see the help pages for each service.  Life Without Limbs can be reached at 818-706-3300, or send an email to info@lifewithoutlimbs.org or send us mail to PO Box 2430, Agoura Hills, CA  91376.

**Links**  
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by Life Without Limbs services are developed by people over whom Life Without Limbs exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.

Life Without Limbs may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of Life Without Limbs programs and services.

**Changes to this Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

**Question/Comments**  
If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time.

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, you are invited to contact us at 818-706-3300, or send an email to info@lifewithoutlimbs.org or send us mail to PO Box 2430, Agoura Hills, CA  91376.
